Responsible Privacy Policy - North Sky Capital                            

Privacy Policy
--------------

North Sky cares about your privacy. We collect your name, e-mail address, the name of your fund and other information you input if you contact North Sky through our “Contact Us” link on this website. We do not otherwise collect personally identifiable information about you over this website. We do not release any personally identifiable information about you to advertisers or other third parties, except as required by law or to a successor or assign in the event of a sale of assets or transfer in ownership. We do use personally identifiable information that we collect to respond to your inquiry and for our own internal purposes. North Sky uses commercially reasonable efforts to protect your personally identifiable information. We cannot, however, guarantee the security of your personally identifiable information. Accordingly, we assume no liability for disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties. Our website may contain links to websites operated by other entities. Please be aware that North Sky is not responsible for the security, content or privacy policies of other websites to which it may link. This Privacy Statement applies to personally identifiable information that North Sky collects on this website. Material changes to this privacy policy will be posted here. Your continued use of this website after any changes are posted will be considered acceptance of those changes.

### We’d like to hear from you.

© 2024 North Sky Capital

### Stay updated

Subscribe to the North Sky Capital newsletter

© 2024 North Sky Capital
